Indiana University President's Office records, 1937-1962 C213
Indiana University Archives
- Subject files, 1937-1962
  - Safety, 1950-1962; (13 folders) (Box 485)
    - Parking, 1955-1962; (8 folders) (Box 485)
    - Regulations, 1945-1946 (Box 485)
  - Saint, 1943-1961; (19 folders) (Box 485)
  - St. Louis Post Dispatch (Box 486)
  - Sal, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 486)
  - Salary, 1938-1952; (25 folders) (Box 486)
  - Sales Conference, 1939-1940 (Box 486)
  - Sales Training Course for Ex-Servicemen of Others, 1945-1946 (Box 486)
  - Sam, 1937-1955; (10 folders) (Box 486)
  - San, 1937-1942; (5 folders) (Box 486)
  - San, 1942-1962; (20 folders) (Box 487)
  - Sanders, Chauncey, 1937-1947 (Box 487)
  - Sanders, Dean Robert L., 1937-1947; (15 folders) (Box 487)
  - Sanitation Reports, 1948-1949 (Box 487)
  - Santarossa Mosaic and Tile Company, 1937-1938 (Box 487)
  - San Francisco Conference, Charter (Box 487)
  - Sar, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 488)
  - Sau, 1952-1955; (3 folders) (Box 488)
  - Sauvain, Dr. H.C., 1937-1952; (13 folders) (Box 488)
  - Sav, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 488)
  - Save the Children Federation, inc., 1944-1945 (Box 488)
  - Savings and Loan Associations, 1950-1951 (Box 488)
  - Say, 1947-1949; (2 folders) (Box 488)
  - Sc, 1937-1955; (18 folders) (Box 488)
  - Sc, 1955-1962; (7 folders) (Box 489)
  - Sch, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 489)
  - Scha, 1944-1962; (18 folders) (Box 489)
  - Schaf, 1937-1944; (7 folders) (Box 489)
  - Sche, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 489)
  - Schedule Committee, 1948-1960; (9 folders) (Box 489)
  - Schedule of Lecturers and Recitations, 1949-1961; (10 folders) (Box 489)
  - Scheibel, Gail, 1947-1948 (Box 489)
  - Scheidt, Albert H., 1948-1949 (Box 489)
  - Schi, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 489)
  - Schi, 1941-1962; (21 folders) (Box 490)
  - Schl, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 490)
  - Schlafer, George E., 1937-1938 (Box 490)
  - Schm, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 490)
  - Schn, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 490)
  - Schneider, Erle Robert, 1944-1945 (Box 490)
  - Scho, 1937-1950; (13 folders) (Box 490)
  - Scho, 1950-1962; (12 folders) (Box 491)
  - Scholarships, 1942-1958; (50 folders) (Box 491)
  - Scholarships, 1958-1961; (3 folders) (Box 492)
  - Merit Scholarships, 1940-1947; (7 folders) (Box 492)
  - Science Scholarships, 1947-1948 (Box 492)
  - State Scholarships, 1939-1940 (Box 492)
  - Wendell Wilkie Scholarships, 1947-1948 (Box 492)
  - Scholarship Rating Study, 1947-1948 (Box 492)
  - Scholastic Records, 1951-1952 (Box 492)
  - School Fund Laws, 1942-1943 (Box 492)
  - School Management, 1959-1962; (3 folders) (Box 492)
  - Schr, 1937-1962; (23 folders) (Box 492)
  - Schr, 1950-1952; (2 folders) (Box 492)
  - Schramm, Jacob Richard, 1954-1960 (Box 492)
  - Schricker, Governor Henry F., 1940-1953; (10 folders) (Box 492)
  - Schu, 1937-1958; (21 folders) (Box 492)
  - Schu, 1958-1961; (4 folders) (Box 493)
  - Schult, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 493)
  - Schum, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 493)
  - Schuman, Dr. Edith Boyer, 1939-1951; (12 folders) (Box 493)
  - Schw, 1937-1962; (24 folders) (Box 493)
  - Science Education Candidates (Box 493)
  - Science Hall Elevator, 1938-1939 (Box 493)
  - Science Hall Repairs and Remodeling, 1938-1939 (Box 493)
  - Science Talent Search, 1944-1945 (Box 493)
  - Sco, 1937-1954; (17 folders) (Box 493)
  - Sco, 1954-1962; (8 folders) (Box 494)
  - Scott, John E., 1937-1942; (3 folders) (Box 494)
  - Scott, Prof. Will and Mrs. Naomi, 1937-1938 (Box 494)
  - Scottish Rite Diamond Jubilee, 1940-1949; (7 folders) (Box 494)
  - Scout Conference, 1938-1939 (Box 494)
  - Scrap Sales, 1945-1946 (Box 494)
  - Self-Survey, 1937-1938 (Box 494)
    (See Box 495A for full report)
  - Se, 1937-1956; (19 folders) (Box 494)
  - Se, 1956-1963; (7 folders) (Box 495)
  - Sea, 1947-1955; (8 folders) (Box 495)
  - Sebeok, Thomas A., 1943-1962; (5 folders) (Box 495)
  - Sec, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 495)
  - Secretary of the Board Trustees Duties, 1938-1939 (Box 495)
  - Security Institute, 1957-1958 (Box 495)
  - Seehausen, Paul, 1946-1950; (4 folders) (Box 495)
  - Sei, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 495)
  - Seismograph, 1947-1948 (Box 495)
  - Sel, 1937-1955; (11 folders) (Box 495)
  - Selective Service System, 1940-1941 (Box 495)
  - Report of the Self-Survey Committee to the Board of Trustees of Indiana University (Box 495A)
    - Part I: Chapters 1-7 (Box 495A)
    - Part II: Chapters 8-14 (Box 495A)
  - Selective Service System, 1941-1949; (7 folders) (Box 496)
  - Self, 1939-1940 (Box 496)
  - Self-Survey, 1937-1940; (12 folders) (Box 496)
  - Sembower, Charles J., 1937-1939; (2 folders) (Box 496)
  - Sembower, Charles J. - "Scholastic Record of Athletes for School Year 1937-1938 at Indiana University" (Box 496)
  - Sembower, John F., 1946-1949; (2 folders) (Box 496)
  - Sen, 1941-1962; (21 folders) (Box 496)
  - Ser, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 496)
  - Service-Clubs, 1939-1940 (Box 496)
    - Enterprises, 1941-1948; (8 folders) (Box 496)
  - Service Enterprises, 1953-1960; (6 folders) (Box 497)
  - Services, IU, 1939-1940 (Box 497)
  - Sesquicentennial History of Indiana, 1956-1959 (Box 497)
  - Sevitsky, Mr. and Mrs. Fabian, 1939-1956; (17 folders) (Box 497)
  - Sewage Service, 1939-1940 (Box 497)
  - Sewers Constructed by I.U., 1946-1947 (Box 497)
  - Sh, 1937-1957; (20 folders) (Box 497)
  - Sha, 1941-1948; (7 folders) (Box 497)
  - Sha, 1948-1955; (7 folders) (Box 498)
  - Shaffer, Frederick E., 1940-1941 (Box 498)
  - Shaffer, Robert H., 1942-1956 (Box 498)
  - Shake, Judge Curtis G., 1938-1939 (Box 498)
  - Shan, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 498)
  - Shane, Harold, 1959-1960 (Box 498)
  - Shar, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 498)
  - Shav, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 498)
  - She, 1937-1958; (21 folders) (Box 498)
  - She, 1958-1962; (4 folders) (Box 499)
  - Sheen, Fulton J, 1950-1959 (Box 499)
  - Shel, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 499)
  - Shep, 1941-1962; (21 folders) (Box 499)
  - Sheppard-Robinson Bill, 1940-1941 (Box 499)
  - Sher, 1937-1955; (10 folders) (Box 499)
  - Shi, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 499)
  - Sho, 1937-1955; (7 folders) (Box 499)
  - Sh, 1957-1960; (3 folders) (Box 499)
  - Sh, 1960-1962; (2 folders) (Box 500)
  - Shoemaker, Colonel Raymond L. (Box 500)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 500)
    - 1941-1942 (Box 500)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 500)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 500)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 500)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 500)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 500)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 500)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 500)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 500)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 500)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 500)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 500)
  - Shook, Charles H. (Box 500)
  - State Life Insurance Company Property, 1952-1953 (Box 500)
  - Shortridge Site File, 1952-1953 (Box 500)
  - Showboat (Box 500)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 500)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 500)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 500)
  - Showalter Foundation Dedication, 1961-1962 (Box 500)
  - Shriner, Ralph L., 1941-1947; (7 folders) (Box 500)
  - Shrivenham American University, 1945-1946 (Box 500)
  - Shu, 1949-1955; (6 folders) (Box 500)
  - Si, 1937-1955; (18 folders) (Box 500)
  - Si, 1955-1962; (7 folders) (Box 501)
  - Siassi Convocation, 1945 (Box 501)
  - Siassi, Dr. Ali Akbar, 1945-1949; (4 folders) (Box 501)
  - Sick Leave for I.U. Staff Members, 1939-1940 (Box 501)
  - Signature Cards, 1947-1948 (Box 501)
  - Sig, 1949-1955; (6 folders) (Box 501)
  - Sigma Nu, 1938-1941; (3 folders) (Box 501)
  - Sikes, P.S., 1940-1953; (14 folders) (Box 501)
  - Sil, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 501)
  - Silberman, E. and A. Galleries, 1939-1940 (Box 501)
  - Sim, 1937-1954; (17 folders) (Box 501)
  - Sim, 1954-1962; (8 folders) (Box 502)
  - Sim, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 502)
  - Simonson, Lee, 1939-1940 (Box 502)
  - Simpson Tree Company, 1937-1938 (Box 502)
  - Sin, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 502)
  - Sinclair, Upton, 1957 (Box 502)
  - Sk, 1937-1962; (24 folders) (Box 502)
  - Skating, 1952-1953 (Box 502)
  - Skinner, Dr. B.F. (Box 502)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 502)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 502)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 502)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 502)
  - Sklanczenko, Tatianna, 1953-1961 (Box 502)
  - Skornia, H.J., 1943-1953; (10 folders) (Box 502)
  - Sl, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 503)
  - Slavic Club, 1949-1959 (Box 503)
  - Slavic Language and Area Department, 1961-1962 (Box 503)
  - Slavic Languages and Literatures, 1960-1962; (2 folders) (Box 503)
  - Slavic Studies, 1948-1958; (3 folders) (Box 503)
  - Sle, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 503)
  - Sm, 1937-1958; (21 folders) (Box 503)
  - Sm, 1958-1962; (4 folders) (Box 504)
  - Small Business Administration, 1956-1957 (Box 504)
  - Smit, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 504)
  - Smith, 1937-1946; (18 folders) (Box 504)
  - Smith, 1946-1955; (18 folders) (Box 505)
  - Smith, Carleton, 1958-1959 (Box 505)
  - Smith, David, 1954-1955 (Box 505)
  - Smith, Henry Holmes, 1948-1955 (Box 505)
  - Smith, H.L., 1937-1938 (Box 505)
  - Smith, H.L., 1937-1945; (27 folders) (Box 506)
  - Smith, H.L., 1945-1947; (3 folders) (Box 507)
  - Smith, James Lee, 1940-1941 (Box 507)
  - Smith, U.H., 1937-1938 (Box 507)
  - Smithwood Center (Trees Center), 1947-1951 (Box 507)
  - Smithwood Cold Storage Plant (Box 507)
    - Annual reports, 1950-1960; (4 folders) (Box 507)
    - General, 1947-1951 (Box 507)
  - Smithwood Hall (Daniel Read Residence Center), 1955 (Box 507)
  - Smithwood Property, 1937-1938 (Box 507)
  - Smo, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 507)
  - Sn, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 507)
  - Snyder, Henry Burgess, 1940-1943; (2 folders) (Box 507)
  - Snyder, William Henry, 1947-1961; (14 folders) (Box 507)
  - So, 1937-1939; (2 folders) (Box 507)
  - So, 1939-1962; (23 folders) (Box 508)
  - Soc, 1947-1948 (Box 508)
  - Social Committee Report for I.U., 1940-1943; (2 folders) (Box 508)
  - Social Security Board, 1937-1938 (Box 508)
  - Social Security, 1954-1957; (4 folders) (Box 508)
  - Division of Social Science, 1954-1955 (Box 509)
  - Division of Social Service (Box 509)
    - Social work degrees, 1911-1945 (Box 509)
    - General (Box 509)
      - 1944-1945 (Box 509)
      - 1945-1946 (Box 509)
      - 1946-1947 (Box 509)
      - 1948-1949 (Box 509)
      - 1949-1950 (Box 509)
      - 1950-1951 (Box 509)
      - 1951-1952 (Box 509)
      - 1952-1953 (Box 509)
      - 1953-1954 (Box 509)
      - 1954-1955 (Box 509)
      - 1955-1956 (Box 509)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 509)
      - 1957-1958 (Box 509)
      - 1958-1959 (Box 509)
      - 1959-1960 (Box 509)
      - 1960-1961 (Box 509)
      - 1961-1962 (Box 509)
    - Annual reports (Box 509)
      - 1944-1945 (Box 509)
      - 1945-1946 (Box 509)
      - 1946-1947 (Box 509)
      - 1947-1948 (Box 509)
      - 1948-1949 (Box 509)
      - 1949-1950 (Box 509)
      - 1950-1951 (Box 509)
      - 1951-1952 (Box 509)
      - 1952-1953 (Box 509)
      - 1953-1954 (Box 509)
      - 1954-1955 (Box 509)
      - 1955-1956 (Box 509)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 509)
      - 1957-1958 (Box 509)
      - 1958-1959 (Box 509)
      - 1959-1960 (Box 509)
      - 1960-1961 (Box 509)
      - 1961-1962 (Box 509)
  - Social Science Survey Course, 1940-1941 (Box 509)
  - Social Work, 1943-1944 (Box 509)
  - Societas Rosicruciana, 1956-1962; (16 folders) (Box 509)
  - Department of Sociology (Box 509)
    - Applications, 1939-1940 (Box 509)
    - Seminar on Theory and Problems of Large Scale Organization, 1961 (Box 509)
    - Annual report, 1961-1962 (Box 509)
  - Socony-Vacuum Oil Company, 1948-1949 (Box 509)
  - Sol, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 509)
  - Somers, George, 1941-1942 (Box 509)
  - Son, 1937-1962; (19 folders) (Box 509)
  - Sonneborn, Tracy M., 1939-1961 (Box 509)
  - Sou, 1937-1955; (10 folders) (Box 509)
  - South Bend Tribune, 1947-1948 (Box 509)
  - South Hall, 1938-1939 (Box 509)
  - Southern Indiana, inc., 1952-1960; (4 folders) (Box 509)
  - Southern Indiana School Men's Club, 1938-1939 (Box 509)
  - Southern Regional Education Board, 1960-1961 (Box 509)
  - Sowerwine, Joe G., 1939-1940 (Box 509)
  - Sp, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 509)
  - Sp, 1941-1962; (21 folders) (Box 510)
  - Space Requests, 1949-1950 (Box 510)
  - Space Utilization, 1949-1950 (Box 510)
  - Space Meeting, 1951-1953 (Box 510)
  - Space, 1953-1954 (Box 510)
  - Space Requests, 1953-1954 (Box 510)
  - Space, 1954-1955 (Box 510)
  - Space, 1955-1958; (3 folders) (Box 511)
  - Spalding, Eugenia K., 1948-1950; (3 folders) (Box 511)
  - Department of Spanish / Spanish and Portuguese, 1942-1961 (Box 511)
  - Spe, 1937-1956; (10 folders) (Box 511)
  - Special Examination Fee, 1937-1938 (Box 511)
  - I.U. Traveling Speech and Hearing Clinic, 1938-1941; (3 folders) (Box 511)
  - Special Semester, 1942-1945; (3 folders) (Box 511)
  - Speech and Hearing Clinic, 1937-1962; (21 folders) (Box 511)
  - Speech and Theatre, 1958-1961; (2 folders) (Box 511)
  - Speeches - Inauguration, 1941-1959 (Box 511)
  - Spi, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 511)
  - Spies, Tom D. (Box 511)
  - Spoor, J.S., 1941-1942 (Box 511)
  - Sports News Service, 1953-1957; (4 folders) (Box 511)
  - Sports News Service, 1959-1962; (4 folders) (Box 512)
  - Spr, 1937-1955; (12 folders) (Box 512)
  - St, 1937-1948; (11 folders) (Box 512)
  - St, 1949-1962; (12 folders) (Box 513)
  - Stadium, 1938-1962; (4 folders) (Box 513)
  - Staf, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 513)
  - Staff Recognition Program, 1962 (Box 513)
  - Stahr, Elvis J. Jr. (Box 513)
  - Stal, 1941-1962; (21 folders) (Box 513)
  - Stalcup, John William, 1946-1947 (Box 513)
  - Stan, 1937-1955; (11 folders) (Box 513)
  - Stanford University, 1937-1938; (2 folders) (Box 513)
  - Standiford, Col. W.R., 1937-1938 (Box 513)
  - Stanford University, 1939-1951; (13 folders) (Box 513)
  - Stapley, Maurice Earl (Box 513)
  - Star, 1937-1947; (10 folders) (Box 513)
  - Star, 1947-1962; (15 folders) (Box 514)
  - Starkey, Otis P., 1946-1953; (7 folders) (Box 514)
  - Starr, Prof. George W., 1937-1942; (2 folders) (Box 514)
  - Statistical and Research Committee, 1937-1938 (Box 514)
  - Statisticians (Box 514)
  - Statistics, 1937-1943; (7 folders) (Box 514)
  - State Assembly Women's Club, 1950-1951 (Box 514)
  - State Basketball Tournament, 1941-1942 (Box 514)
  - State Drama Conference, 1938-1939 (Box 514)
  - State Government Conference, 1941-1942 (Box 514)
  - State Highways, 1941-1942 (Box 514)
  - State of the University, 1947-1954; (2 folders) (Box 514)
  - State Road #37, 1939-1940; (2 folders) (Box 514)
  - State Universities and Private Schools – Comparisons, 1940 (Box 514)
  - Statistics, 1942-1945 (Box 514)
  - Ste, 1937-1951; (14 folders) (Box 514)
  - Ste, 1951-1962; (11 folders) (Box 515)
  - Stearns, Marshall (Box 515)
    - 1942-1944 (Box 515)
    - February 1945-May 1946 (Box 515)
    - June 1946-January 1947 (Box 515)
  - Stechert, G.E. and Co., 1945-1946 (Box 515)
  - Stee, 1948-1950; (2 folders) (Box 515)
  - Steele, Selma, 1939-1945 (Box 515)
  - Stei, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 515)
  - Steiner, Prof. George, 1938-1943; (4 folders) (Box 515)
  - Stel, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 515)
  - Stempel, Guido, 1937-1938 (Box 515)
  - Stempel, John E. (Box 515)
    - 1937-1951, (16 folders) (Box 515)
    - 1951-1962, (10 folders) (Box 515A)
  - Stenographic Applications, 1938-1939 (Box 515A)
  - Stenographic and Secretarial Positions (Box 515A)
  - Step, 1941-1947; (6 folders) (Box 515A)
  - Step, 1947-1962; (15 folders) (Box 516)
  - Stephens, Dan V., 1938-1939 (Box 516)
  - Ster, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 516)
  - Stet, 1941-1962; (21 folders) (Box 516)
  - Stev, 1937-1955; (10 folders) (Box 516)
  - Stevenson, Elizabeth, 1938-1939 (Box 516)
  - Stevenson, Dean R.A.-Bill, 1938-1939; (6 folders) (Box 516)
  - Stew, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 516)
  - Stewart, John Lee, 1940-1943; (3 folders) (Box 516)
  - Stewart, John Lee, 1943-1944 (Box 517)
  - Sti, 1937-1955; (12 folders) (Box 517)
  - Sto, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 517)
  - Ston, 1937-1954; (17 folders) (Box 517)
  - Ston, 1954-1962; (8 folders) (Box 518)
  - Stone, Florence Herz, 1937-1938 (Box 518)
  - Stone, Thornton, 1940-1950; (10 folders) (Box 518)
  - Stoner, Richard B., 1939-1955 (Box 518)
  - Stores and Service Building, 1937-1938 (Box 518)
  - Storesroom, 1947-1962; (27 folders) (Box 518)
  - Stout, Selatie E., 1937-1942; (16 folders) (Box 518)
  - Stout, Rufus Sea, 1941-1950 (Box 518)
  - Stout, Selatie E., 1942-1943; (4 folders) (Box 519)
  - Stout, W.H., 1937-1939; (2 folders) (Box 519)
  - Stowkowski, Leopold, 1940-1941 (Box 519)
  - Str, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 519)
  - Strain, William H. (Records and Admissions) (Box 519)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 519)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 519)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 519)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 519)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 519)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 519)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 519)
  - Strauss, A.M., 1937-1953; (17 folders) (Box 519)
  - Stre, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 519)
  - Dr. Wolfgang Stresemann Address, 1960-1961 (Box 519)
  - Strickland Grievance Case, 1949-1950 (Box 519)
  - Strickland, Ruth G., 1939-1961 (Box 519)
  - Strikes on University Buildings, 1939-1940 (Box 519)
  - Stro, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 519)
  - Stud, 1937-1955; (17 folders) (Box 520)
  - Studebaker, J.W., 1938-1939 (Box 520)
  - Student Employment Service (Box 520)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 520)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 520)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 520)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 520)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 520)
  - Student, 1943-1962; (17 folders) (Box 520)
  - Student Activities Office (Box 520)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 520)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 520)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 520)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 520)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 520)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 520)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 520)
  - Students, 1937-1939; (2 folders) (Box 520)
  - Student Artist Program, 1944-1945 (Box 520)
  - Student Building and Association of Women Students, Annual reports (Box 520)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 520)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 520)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 520)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 520)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 520)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 520)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 520)
  - Student Building - Suggestions for the Use of, 1939-1940 (Box 520)
  - Student Booklet (Box 520)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 520)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 520)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 520)
  - Student Contact Program, 1939-1940 (Box 520)
    (RESTRICTED)
  - Student Council (Box 520)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 520)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 520)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 520)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 520)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 520)
  - Student Directory, 1949-1959; (10 folders) (Box 520)
  - Student and Educational Services, 1956-1957 (Box 521)
  - Student Activities, 1958-1959 (Box 521)
  - Student and Educational Services, Division of, 1950-1958 (Box 521)
    - Annual report (Box 521)
      - 1951-1952 (Box 521)
      - 1952-1953 (Box 521)
      - 1953-1954 (Box 521)
      - 1954-1955 (Box 521)
      - 1955-1956 (Box 521)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 521)
      - 1957-1958 (Box 521)
    - Director, 1956-1957 (Box 521)
  - Student Exchanges, Work Camp, Youth Service, etc., 1948-1949 (Box 521)
  - Student Expenditures (Box 521)
    - Letter sent to Congressmen and State Representatives and Senators, 1939-1939 (Box 521)
      (Did not scan duplicate letters Wells sent to politicians.)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 521)
  - Student Guidance (Box 521)
    - Annual report, 1939-1940 (Box 521)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 521)
  - Student Handbook, 1946-1947 (Box 521)
  - Student Health, 1937-1962; (35 folders) (Box 521)
  - Student Loan, 1937-1962; (27 folders) (Box 521)
  - (Law School) Freshman Guidance and Research Program Annual report, 1950-1951 (Box 521)
  - Guidance and Placement Bureau (Box 521)
    - Two-Year report, 1942-1944 (Box 521)
    - Annual report, 1944-1945 (Box 521)
  - Student League, 1939-1940 (Box 521)
  - Students, Letters to parents and their replies, 1947-1948 (Box 521)
  - Indiana University Student Loan Service Annual report (Box 521)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 521)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 521)
  - Student Loans and Halls Accounts Unpaid, 1947-1948 (Box 521)
  - Student Mortality – Number of students who did not re-enter university, 1940 (Box 521)
  - Student, 1953-1955; (2 folders) (Box 521)
  - Student Organizations (Box 521)
    - Funds reports (Box 521)
      - 1937-1938 (Box 521)
      - 1939-1940 (Box 521)
      - 1944-1945 (Box 521)
    - Major ones, 1938-1939 (Box 521)
    - esp. Young Socialist Alliance (YSA), 1961-1962m (Box 521)
    - Fair Play for Cuba, 1961-1962 (Box 521)
  - Division of Student Personnel Annual report (Box 521)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 521)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 521)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 521)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 521)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 521)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 521)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 521)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 521)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 521)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 521)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 521)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 521)
  - Student Personnel Records, 1941-1942 (Box 521)
  - Student Refugee Committee, 1939-1940 (Box 521)
  - Division of Student Personnel (Box 522)
  - Student Picketing, 1945-1946 (Box 522)
  - Student Publications Board, 1954-1959; (2 folders) (Box 522)
  - Student Radical, 1939-1940 (Box 522)
  - Student Representatives, 1943 (Box 522)
  - Student Self-Government, 1940-1941 (Box 522)
  - Student Senate (Box 522)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 522)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 522)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 522)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 522)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 522)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 522)
    - 1958/1959 (Box 522)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 522)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 522)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 522)
  - Student In Service, 1943-1945; (2 folders) (Box 522)
  - Student Supreme Court Cases, 1948-1954 (Box 522)
  - Student Union, 1939-1953; (3 folders) (Box 522)
  - Student War Council (Box 522)
    - 1941-1942 (Box 522)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 522)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 522)
  - Student Studies, ca., 1940 (Box 522)
  - Su, 1937-1961; (24 folders) (Box 522)
  - Su, 1961-1962 (Box 523)
  - Su, Ting, 1956-1959; (3 folders) (Box 523)
  - Sub-Administrative Group, 1958-1959; (2 folders) (Box 523)
  - Sudershanam, N. George, 1961-1962 (Box 523)
  - Sugar Situation, 1942-1943 (Box 523)
  - Sul, 1952-1955; (3 folders) (Box 523)
  - Sulzer, Elmer G. (Box 523)
  - Sum, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 523)
  - Summer Session, 1939-1961; (58 folders) (Box 523)
  - Summer Session, 1949-1962; (40 folders) (Box 524)
  - Summer Session, 1958-1962; (11 folders) (Box 525)
  - Summer Sessions – Comparison, Purdue and Indiana University, 1940 (Box 525)
  - Summer Theatre, 1939-1940 (Box 525)
  - Summers, Charles E., 1938-1939 (Box 525)
  - Superior Students (Box 525)
  - Supplies – Method for Procuring, 1947; (legal size) (Box 525)
  - Sur, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 525)
  - Surplus Property, 1944-1951; (6 folders) (Box 525)
  - Survey Courses, 1939-1942; (2 folders) (Box 525)
  - Survey Lists (Box 525)
  - Survey, 1958-1959; (11 folders) (Box 525)
  - Self-Survey, 1939-1940; (2 folders) (Box 525)
  - Survey Committee (Box 525)
  - Self-Survey, 1938-1939 (Box 525)
  - Survey File, 1958-1959; (2 folders) (Box 525)
  - Endowment Income for the Cost of Investment Services, 1958-1959 (Box 525)
  - License Fess to ASCAP, 1958-1959 (Box 525)
  - Survey, 1956; (3 folders) (Box 525)
  - Survey – University of California Defense Security Agreement, 1951 (Box 525)
  - Sutherland, Prof. E.H., 1937-1948; (12 folders) (Box 525)
  - Sutherland, Richard G. (Box 525)
  - Sw, 1937-1954; (16 folders) (Box 525)
  - Sw, 1954-1962; (8 folders) (Box 526)
  - Swan, Walter, 1944-1945 (Box 526)
  - Swain Hall, 1940-1947; (3 folders) (Box 526)
  - Swarthmore College, 1937-1949; (12 folders) (Box 526)
  - Swe, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 526)
  - Swi, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 526)
  - Swiggett, Dr. G.L., 1939-1940; (2 folders) (Box 526)
  - Swimming Pool, 1937-1939; (2 folders) (Box 526)
  - Swindler, Dr. Mary, 1940-1941 (Box 526)
  - Sy, 1937-1955; (12 folders) (Box 526)
  - Symons, Virginia Thompson, 1953 (Box 526)
  - Syncardon, 1955-1956 (Box 526)
  - T, 1937-1947; (10 folders) (Box 526)
  - T, 1947-1962; (15 folders) (Box 527)